（伊利诺伊州 芝加哥市）
这儿实在是
This place is.
太漂亮了
Beautiful.
还 还好吧
It's…all right.
你今晚很漂亮
You're beautiful.
听着 Roth
Look, Roth.
如果你觉得甜言蜜语
If you think laying it on thick like that.
就能有什么进展的话
Is gonna get you somewhere tonight.
- 我就想对了吗 - 你就想太对了
- I'm right? - You're totally right.
不闹了 说真的
Okay, spill.
为什么带我来这儿
Why are we here.
先别急
Hold that thought.
Roth先生
Mr.Roth.
今晚很隆重啊
I heard it's a big night.
嗯 最隆重的一次
Yeah, the biggest.
你能把这个放在香槟酒里吗
Can you put this in a glass of champagne.
或者其他什么里面
Something nice.
真是独特
How unique.
Sal
Sal.
好久不见
Long time no see.
是啊 太久了 Maurice
Too long, Maurice.
- 最近怎么样 - 还好
- How've you been, man? - Good.
- 你怎么样 - 不错
- How are you doing - Good.
见到你真好
Good to see you.
喂
Dude.
我们刚在说话
We were just talking.
有问题吗
Is that a problem.
没事的 Marv
No, chill out, Marv.
有事吗
It's all good.
- 嗯 - 没事
- Yeah? - Yeah.
这边请 先生们
This way gentlemen.
最近怎么样
How've you been.
很好 Lassiter先生
Good Mr.Lassiter.Good.
时而出力 时而收获
Sometimes you give and sometimes you get.
有时候你真的能收获许多
Sometimes you really get.
嘿Mindy
Hey, Mindy.
想我了吗
Miss me.
我喜欢金发的你
Aww, I liked you as a blonde.
这样呢 我听说你们进了点儿好东西
Better?I hear they have more fun.
Julian
Hello, Julian.
我不是来找麻烦的
I'm not looking for trouble.
我只想喝杯酒
I just want a drink.
我还想吃Taylor Swift的心呢
And I want to eat Taylor Swift's heart.
但是我们不总能得到我们想要的
But we can't always get what we want.
挪一挪你的变形怪屁股 赶紧滚
Now get your shifter ass out of here.
我不是在问你
I wasn't asking.
你们这群狼人
You werewolves.
你们觉得你们高人一等
You think you're so special.
事实上不过是一群狗娘养的的杂种
And really you're just sons of bitches.
- 就这点儿能耐 - 相信我 蠢货
- That all you got - Oh trust me, slugger.
比这要多
I got more.
多多了
So much more.
你跑哪儿去 虚张声势的胆小鬼
Where're you going you yeller.
Ennis
Ennis.
我们去哪儿
Where are we going.
那里面
That place.
不是我们的天地
That wasn't us.
所以你把我拉上渡轮码头是要干什么
So you dragged me to a ferry stop, why.
我们就是在渡轮上相遇的 八年级那次出游
We met on a ferry, that field trip, 8th grade.
你编了长辫子
You have your hair in braids and.
我的目光就再也离不开你
And I couldn't take my eyes off you.
Tam
Tam.
现在只有我们两个
This is us.
- 所以 - 我的天啊
- So - Oh my god.
快报警
Call 911.
David 对不起
David, I'm sorry.
David 谁是David
David?Who's David.
我没有其他选择
I don't have a choice.
Tamara
Tamara.
（北芝加哥大学）
W.L.Graham
数学系主任.
主任
Professor.
您在这里做什么
What're you doing here.
我去下办公室 你怎么没去吃午饭
My office.Why aren't you at lunch.
一些文件要看
Paper work.
我以为你和你妻子
I thought you and your wife.
这个周末出去了
Have gone away for the weekend.
我们是 我只是
We have, we are, I just.
忘了点儿东西
Forgot something.
没什么好担心的
Don't worry about it.
（Margo来电）
Matt 我是David Lassiter
Matt, it's David Lassiter.
散布消息
Spread the word.
我已经拿到数学答案了
I've got an answer to the math final.
50美元一个人
50 bucks a pop.
Teddy的彩陶馆 我是小肉桂
Teddy's house of pinatas, cinnamon speaking.
一点都不好笑 该死的 David你到底在哪儿
Not funny, David where the hell are you.
你需要回家一趟
You need to come home.
Margo，Margo镇静点
Margo, Margo, slow down.
David听我说
David, listen to me.
你先必须回家
You have to come home now.
怎么了
What do you mean.
是Sal出事了
It's about Sal.
Sal怎么了
What about Sal.
我们的哥哥死了
Our brother is dead.
我清楚我到底看到了什么
I know what I saw.
你真的确定吗
Are you sure.
我是说 确定吗
I mean…sure.
因为你告诉我你看到了一个
Cause what you're telling me.
那个面目全非的怪物
About this faceless whatever-it-is.
那东西有爪子
That thing has claws.
可能 当时你有些迷糊
Look, maybe you are confused.
可能是拿着刀的小混混什么的
Maybe maybe with some banger with a knife.
我知道我到底看到什么了
I know what I saw.
我是想帮你
I am trying to help.
把我当做骗子是帮我吗
By calling me a liar.
你和你爸简直一模一样
You are just like your old man.
Nate Ross 他是位很出色的警察
Nate Ross, he's a great cop.
教会了我很多
He tought me everything I know.
但是他的脾气却一直坏事
But his temper never did many favors.
听着 我知道你很不容易
Look, you had a tough break.
那么小就没有了爸爸
Losing your dad as young as you did.
我已经尽我所能在帮忙了
And I have done all that I can to help.
但是如果你再这样不分黑白地
But if you go But if you go off half-cocked.
满口乱喷怪物什么的胡话
Spouting this monster crap.
或者继续做蠢事的话
Or doing something stupid.
我也帮不了你什么了 Ennis
I can't help you anymore, Ennis.
我知道我看到的是什么
I know what I saw.
探员Bonhan和Peart
Agent Bonham and Peart.
FBI 接下来交给我们吧
FBI we will take it from here.
不可能
Like hell you will.
FBI什么时候对持刀伤人的案子感兴趣了
Since when did the Feebs start working on stabbings.
听着 探长
Listen, ditective.
这个惯犯和之前的描述很相符
Perp fits a certain profile.
我可以给你说明细节 但是我懒得跟你废话
Now, I could go into detail, but I'm, I'm not going to.
我们来聊聊昨天晚上吧
Alright, let's talk about last night.
怎么 你们也想说我疯了
Why?Do you call me crazy too.
说一说也无妨
Try us.
我到她身边时 她
When I got to her.
她已经
She…she's.
你已经无能为力了
There was nothing you could have done.
我想 你说这话是想安慰我吧
I suppose that helps me feel better.
那东西根本不是人类
Look, this thing wasn't human.
所以 你们想怎么对付那东西
So what are you going to do about it.
我也不知道该怎么跟你讲 孩子
I don't know what to tell you, kid.
这世上没有怪物这种东西
There's no such thing as monsters.
Margo 镇定点
Margo, calm down.
别跟我说镇定 探长先生
Don't tell me to calm down, detective.
食尸鬼家族到底愿不愿意支持我们
Just tell me the ghouls, are they with us.
- 可能吧 - 什么叫可能
- Maybe - Maybe.
可能是拿不到钱的 Freddie
We don't pay for maybe, Freddie.
切入正题吧
Cut to the chase.
好吧
Alright, well.
按照你父亲目前的情况
With your pop the way he is.
加上Sal的去世
And now Sal's gone.
各大家族表示很忧虑
Families have concerns.
告诉那群食尸鬼 鬼灵 还是什么的
Tell the ghouls, the Djinn the.
现在是我在管理这个家族
Whoever I run this family now.
尽管放马过来吧
So they can either back ass.
我会把他们打趴下
Or I'll bend them over.
然后把点四五口径的枪对准他们 射空弹夹
Jam a.45 elbow deep and empty the damn clip.
Margo
Margo.
你还真回来了
You actually came.
欢迎回家 David
Welcome home, David.
嘿 Sal的事很抱歉
Hi, sorry about Sal.
他是个 是个好人
He was…he was a good one.
他怎么了
What happened to him.
是Julian Duval干的
Julian Duval happened.
他和Sal在Il Secundo饭店的密室中有了口角
He and Sal had words in the backroom of Il Secundo.
然后那个狼人派人包围了饭店 毁了整个地方
Then the wolf circled around and tore that place apart.
他掏出了Sal的心脏 他会为之付出代价的
He clawed out Sal's heart, and he will bleed for that.
也许你能给她讲讲道理
Maybe you can talk some sense into her.
因为我是没辙了
Cause I sure as hell can't.
Margo
Margo.
这是步枪协会的什么节日吗
What's with the NRA Christmas here.
你想做什么
What are you doing.
我们要走向战争
We are going to war.
你要是不喜欢 去跟爸爸说
You don't like it?Talk to daddy.
我不知道爸爸状况这么不好
I didn't know papa was this bad.
你一走就是三年
You've been gone 3 years.
一切都变了
Things change.
Margo 你确定是Julian吗
Margo, are you sure it was Julian.
有人看见他了
Cause he's got a witness.
亲眼见到Julian了
And saw Julian.
他恨Sal
He hated Sal.
你知道 我知道
You knew it, and I knew.
整个城市都知道
And the whole damn city knew it.
那个混蛋找准了机会 然后就动手了
The dick saw his shot, and he took it.
我不这么觉得
That's a no.
那个杂种杀了我们哥哥
The mutt gutted our brother.
你也不能确定
You don't know that.
如果是狼人做的
And if the werewolves did it.
如果 看看你
If?Look at you.
倾尽全力来保护那个这么多年来
Falling all over yourself to defend the family.
一直骑在我们头上的家族
That's had their foot on our neck for years.
跟以前没什么两样
Just like old times.
顺便说一句
By the way.
你的前任快要结婚了
Your ex is getting married.
你知道的 对吧 Violet
You know that, right, Violet.
她爸把她卖给了纽约的狼人家族
Her father pimped her out to the New York wolves.
为了完成什么交易
To seal some deal.
我不是说不去反抗
I am not saying don't fight.
我只是说好好想想
I am saying being smart.
找出真相
Find out what happened.
- 如果真的是Julian做的 - 你会怎样
- And if Julian did this - Then you what.
行了吧 David
David, come on.
你并不想参与这些
You don't want this.
你逃离家族去做人类
You run away to be a human.
你总是同情他们
You always have a soft spot for them.
既然你走了 就在外边别回来
Look, you are out, stay out.
你真的不来点儿什么吗
You're sure I can't get you anything.
波旁
Bourbon.
血
Blood.
我很好
I'm fine.
你真觉得变形怪们会有所举动吗
Do you really think the shifters will make a move.
Margo可不傻
Margo is not stupid.
Julian
Julian.
现在不行 Violet
Not now, Violet.
我们必须谈谈 求你了
We need to talk, please.
我刚听说Sal Lassiter死了
I just heard Sal Lassiter's dead.
亲爱的 我能为你做什么
Oh, dear, whatever shall I do.
是你杀了他吗
Did you kill him.
不
No.
从他的尸体来看 Sal死的很快
From the look at his body, Sal died quick.
你是在哪儿看见他的尸体的
Where you saw his body.
我观察很仔细 对吧
I'm thorough, ain't I.
那是谁杀了他
Then who killed him.
这不关我的事儿
Like I care.
你为什么要见那个灵怪
Why are you meeting with the Djinn.
因为Margo Lassiter
Because that whore.
那个小贱人想让我死
Margo Lassiter wants me dead.
她认定是我杀了她兄弟
She thinks I sliced up her brother.
那我就只好恭敬不如从命了
Then I'm not gonna tell her any different.
而且变形怪们做的太过了
After what those shifters have done.
在我们的领地上嚣张造势
Chipping away at our territory.
侮辱我们
Insulting us.
战争不可避免
There's a war coming.
我需要那位纹身兄站在我这一边
And I need Tattoo there on my side.
等等 Julian
Wait, Julian, stop.
你在盘算什么
What do you think you are doing.
你就是我们的玩物而已 小公主
You're the bitch in this pack, princess.
你只要打扮得漂漂亮亮的 然后闭上你的嘴
Your job is to be pretty and silent.
打仗 或是不打仗 不是你能决定的
So war, no war, you don't get a vote.
不
No.
Tamara
Tamara.
芝加哥警察
Chicago PD.
待在原地不要动
Stay right where you are.
我不这么认为
I don't think so.
见鬼
What the hell.
这家伙还是没脑袋的时候更顺眼 是不是
He looks better with a little off the top, don't you think.
如果你想跑路的话 现在可以跑了
You wanna run.Now it's the time.
我哪儿都不去
I'm not going any where.
除非有人跟我解释一下这都是怎么回事儿
Until someone tells me what the hell is going on.
你该走了
You should go.
不
No.
好吧 Sammy 你来讲解一下
Alright, Sammy, give him the talk.
听着 我叫Sam Winchester
Alright, look, my name is Sam Winchester.
他是我哥 Dean
That's my brother, Dean.
我们
We uh…
我们猎杀吸血鬼
We kill vampires.
狼人 恶魔 和
And werewolves and demons and.
简单来说 我们追踪鬼怪 然后砍了他们的头
Basically we chase down evil and we cut its head off.
所以你们算什么
So you what.
怪物警察
Monster cops.
猎人
Hunters.
那是什么杀了我女朋友
Then what killed my girlfriend.
我们正在查
We're working on it, okay.
根据你告诉我们的 那东西是个新面孔
And from what you told us, this thing sounds new.
要不就是Freddy Krueger（《猛鬼街》中的反派）
Or Freddy Krueger.
那我从镜子里看到的那个家伙呢
What about that guy I saw in the mirror.
有一张腐烂掉的脸
With a messed up face.
可能是个幽灵
It's probably a Wraith.
很多超自然生物都会以人形出现
Look, a lot of these things can look human.
但是镜子会让他们露出马脚
Until you catch them in the mirror.
或者照相机也可以
Or sometimes a camera.
所以 你们找到那个怪物
So…you find this whatever.
然后你们砍了它的头
And you're gonna chop his head off.
是啊
Yeah.
有时候 要是有顾虑 可以用银弹
Or sometimes, when in doubt try silver bullet.
嘿 Sammy
Hey Sammy.
在
Yeah.
这个柜子里装满了肉和血袋
This is full of blood and meat.
很多生肉
A lot of meat.
事实上这一块
Actually this one.
这一块叫做Susan
This one is labled Susan.
难道这儿是酒吧暗房之类的地方吗
What is this?Some kind of backroom.
怪物VIP密室
Monster VIP.
如果是的话
Yeah, well if it is.
Sal Lassiter之前来过这儿
And Sal Lassiter was here.
所以他不是人类
Then he is not human.
所以呢 现在怪物开始互相残杀了
So what?We've got monster killing monster now.
也许吧 我们找到了尸体
Maybe.We got this in body.
我和你们一起
I'm gonna with you.
不 你留下
No you're gonna stay.
不然呢 你会伤害我吗
Or what, You gonna hurt me.
我爱的女孩死了 我的人生也毁了
Kill the girl I love ruin my damn life.
现在才说这些太晚了吧
Yeah you too late.
听着Ennis
Ennis listen.
相信我 我了解你的感受 我曾经也感同身受
I get it.Believe me, I have been there.
但是我们做的事情 根本不是你能想象的
But what we do, it's messed up.
所以你最好不要搀和进来
So do yourself a favour and stay on.
不然你也会受到牵连的
You will get hurt too.
嗨 我们能谈谈吗
Hey, can we talk.
谈什么
About what.
昨天晚上 杀死Tamara的那个东西
Last night, this thing you think killed Tamara.
它长什么样子
What did it look like.
东西
Thing.
你自己说的 是持刀的小混混干的
You said it was some banger with a knife.
不能放过任何线索嘛 孩子
Chasing out every lead, kid.
我告诉过你 它的脸被蒙住了
Like I told you, it didn't have much of a face.
他 它有没有说过什么
He…it…whatever say anything.
我告诉过你
I told you that too.
那再告诉我一次
Then tell me again.
要是你有时间 为什么不多留一会儿呢
If you got time why don't you hang around.
我老爸还在墓园 但他马上就能回来
Dad's working the graveyard, but he'll be home soon.
他见到你会很开心的
He'd love to see you.
当然
Sure.
同样高兴见到他
Good to see him too.
抱歉 短信
Sorry, text.
没关系
No worries.
我能说什么呢 我知道这很不容易
What can I say…I know this is hard.
昨晚那鬼东西把我的外套划破了
See that thing slashed up my jacket pretty good.
警察已经检查过了 但是
Forensics went over it, but.
你想看看吗
If you wanna see it.
那正好
That will be great.
非常感谢你的合作 孩子
I appreciate it, kid.
真的
Really.
嘿
Hey.
这把枪里装着银弹
There is a sliver bullet in this gun.
Ennis
Ennis.
Ennis 别这样
Ennis, don't.
你不是Freddy Custer 你是谁
You are not Freddy Custer, so who are you.
我的名字是David Lassiter 我是个变形怪
My name is David Lassiter, I am an shapeshifter.
你是什么
You are what.
我们能变形
We shift our shape.
听名字就能大概知道了
It's kind all there in our name.
Sal Lassiter是我的兄弟
Sal Lassiter is my brother.
我只想知道谁杀了他
I just want to find out who killed him.
所以你变成了另外一个人
So you slape on somebody else's faces.
这就是我的能力
It's kinda my go-to.
我看了警方的报告
Look, I read the police report.
我知道你也失去了你重要的人
I know you lost someone, too.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我不想要提到她
See you don't talk about her.
你知道外面发生了什么吗
You know what's going on out there.
你有任何想法吗
Do you have any idea.
怪物 猎人 我大概知道
Yeah, freaks hunters, yeah, I got the basics.
你还真是自身难保啊
Wow!Are you so in over your head.
让我简略的告诉你吧
Let me give you a short version.
芝加哥被五个怪物家族
Chicago has been divided up.
所掌控着
Between five monster families.
你在开玩笑
So, is that a joke.
你听见有人笑了吗
Do you hear the laugh track.
那警察呢
What about the police.
警察是我们的人
We own the police.
听着 上到勒索敲诈
Look I'm talkinga about shakedowns.
下到器官贩卖
Organ Trafficking.
狼人家族在黄金海岸一带影响力颇大
The werewolf threaten the Gold Coast.
灵怪掌握着南部
The Djinn own the South side.
我们不想引人注目
We want to keep the low profile so.
所以我们尽量保持和平
We keep the peace.
这样人类也不会死伤太多
Human casualty is the minimum.
不会死伤太多
A minimum.
我也不想这样 好吗
Look I don't like it either, okay.
但你知道隐藏在和平之下蠢蠢欲动的是什么吗
But do you know what's behind door number two.
战争
War.
人类与怪物在街上血腥的争斗
It's boold.Human and monsters in the street.
但是现在
And right now.
有个人想阻止这一切
There is actually one guy trying to stop it.
听上去真不错
WOW!Good for you.
我真想给你鼓个掌
I'd slow clap but well.
真可惜 我腾不出手
My hands are a little full.
别搀和进来好吗
Just stay out of it, okay.
这些划痕上有银的痕迹
These cuts are flecked with sliver.
你怎么知道
How do you know.
因为它有灼烧感
Cause it burns.
所以呢
So.
Julian Duval可没有银爪子
Julian Duval hasn't got silver claws.
他是一个狼人
He's a werewolf.
听着
So get this.
验尸官说
The…eh…coroner.
有一个叫Julian Duval的人
Says this guy, this Julian Duval.
出3000块要求看一看Sal的尸体
Shows up, drops 3 grand to see Sal's corpse.
他还住在一座城堡里
And he lives in a feaking castle.
这家伙是谁
Who is this guy.
如果我们运气好
If we are lucky.
说不定能在他们的怪物酒馆里碰到几个
Someone might happen to be at their monster bar.
夫人
Madam.
别装了 David
You can cut the act, David.
你怎么发现的
How did you.
我了解你
I know you.
好吧 我也了解你
Yeah, well, ditto.
真的管家现在还好吗
Is the real butler okay.
他去休息了
He's resting.
在壁橱里
Locked in a closet.
你不该来这儿
You shouldn't be here.
你以为我想来吗
You think I wanna be here.
是为了Sal
It's about Sal.
我听说了 我很难过
I heard.I'm so sorry.
不是Julian干的
Julian didn't do it.
我知道
I know.
所以我想让你找他谈谈
That's why I need you to talk to your brother.
和他在酒吧坐下来聊聊
Getting him to sit down at the bar.
我们就能终结这一切
So just we can work this crap out.
这是不可能的
There's no way that's happening.
我们能阻止这场战争 Violet
We can stop a war, Violet.
首先 Julian不想阻止他们
One, Julian doesn't want to stop them.
其次 怎么阻止
Second, how.
你在逃亡 而我 我只是个婊子
You are a runaway and I am, I'm a bitch.
我们无足轻重
We don't matter.
你怎么回事
What's wrong with you.
你什么时候开始对他们服服帖帖的
Since when did you play their game.
你什么时候
Since when.
也开始把责任都推到纽约来的混蛋身上了
Did you lay your debt on some dick from New York.
你以为我有的选吗
You think I had a choice.
当然有
You did.
联合车站 午夜
Union Station, midnight.
你本来可以选的
You had a choice.
你 是你说我们应该离开
You…you are the one who said we should go away.
过平凡的生活
Live a normal life.
你定了时间 地点
You set the time, place.
我去了
I was there.
你又在哪儿
Where were you.
快跑
Run.
Violet
Violet.
到底怎么回事
Hell what's going on.
没什么
It's okay.
你是谁
Who are you.
他叫David Lassiter
His name's David Lassiter.
是个变形怪
He's a shapeshifter.
我们得撤了
Hey we gotta go.
快走 马上
Now.Let's go.
到了 全下车
It's there.Everybody out.
你的意思是
So you are telling me.
整个芝加哥被五个怪物家族统治着
There are five monster families that run Chicago.
这算什么
What is this.
吸血鬼版教父
God Father with fangs.
听着 就算是
Look, if it is.
我也要不惜一切代价报仇
I'm gonna need all the help I can get.
这家伙还真是死脑筋
Well, he doesn't quit.
我算看出来了
I'll give him that.
Violet不接电话
Violet is not picking up.
等等 这个女孩
Wait, so this girl.
她也是变形怪吗
She's a shapeshifter, too.
狼人
Werewolf.
- 酷毙了 - 酷毙了
- Awesome - Awesome.
她带着手机
If she has her cell.
我们就能追踪信号
We could trace the signal.
说不定行得通
Maybe you are right.
行 她手机号多少
Alright, what's her number.
把我也带上
Take me with you.
我会帮你们的
It's all yours.
不行
No.
见鬼 千万别
Hell no.
他妈的他是个变形金刚
Dude, he's a freaking transformer.
有时候你不得和坏人合作
And sometime you gotta work with the bad guys.
才能逮到更坏的人
To get to the worse guys.
伙计 我是透明的吗
Dude, I'm right here.
不 我看见你了
Yeah, I see you.
别以为我也是什么怪胎
You think I'm something freak.
像你一样
Like you.
我才不是
Oh, I'm not.
我只是个凡人
I'm just a man.
有些有趣的小玩具罢了
With some fun little toys.
信号源在那儿
Singal's coming from there.
嘿 谢谢你 还有
Hey, thanks for, you know.
你女朋友的事 我
And about your girlfriend I'm.
我不需要你的道歉
I don't need no apology from you.
我也失去过挚爱
I lost someone, too.
好吗
Okay.
可我一样在努力
But I'm trying here.
你弟弟的事我很抱歉
Sorry about your brother.
他最后有提到你
He spoke about you at the end.
他说 David 对不起
He said, David I'm sorry.
我没得选
I didn't have a choice.
要开房的话待会儿可以吗
You guys can kiss and make up later.
我们还有工作要做 快点
We got work to do, come on.
银器
Silver.
如果你不是人类 是鬼怪的话
It burns if you are evil.
它会灼伤你的皮肤
If you are a monster.
不 不 看着他
No, no, look at him.
那是我儿子
He was my son.
你哥哥 那个变形怪 那个Lassiter
Your brother, the shifter, Lassiter.
把他大卸八块
He ripped him apart.
他们之前告诉我说行凶的是野生动物
They told me it was a wild animal.
很多年来我都深信不疑
I have believed it for years.
但是我现在知道真相了
But now I know the truth.
求你了 Sal和Julian都很恨对方
Please, Sal and Julian hated each other.
但他们不会伤害这个孩子的
Neither of them would hurt the kid.
我为什么要相信你
Why should I believe you.
你已经死了
You're dead.
他们明天就会找到你的尸体
Tomorrow they will find pieces of you.
散落在整个镇子里
All over town.
这些兽类马上就会发狂
All doggies be mad.
这就是你的计划吗
Is that what you wanted.
你想挑起战争
You are trying to start a war.
怪物们之间挑起内讧
Freaks start killing freaks.
我们会赢的
We win.
不 一旦战争开始
No, once it starts.
你有没有想过 有多少人
Do you have any idea how many people.
多少孩子 会因此丧命吗
How many children will die.
你跟我走 罗密欧
You're with me, Romeo.
听着不错 吸血鬼猎人Buffy
Sounds good, Buffy.
Dave Dave
Dave, Dave.
对不起 Violet
I'm so sorry, Violet.
看来我又得杀鸡儆猴了
Guess I'm going to have to make an example of you, too.
不
No.
别伤害她
Don't hurt her.
为什么
Why.
因为她是你女朋友吗
Because she's your girlfriend.
看看你现在说话的样子
Yeah I heard you talking, real sweet.
几乎跟人类没什么区别
Hell it was almost human.
几乎
Almost.
事实是
Here's the thing.
你可以有人类的相貌 人类的行为
You can look human, and act human.
但是内心深处 你仍然是怪兽
But deep down, you're still a monster.
Violet 住手
Violet, no, please.
Violet 别这样
Please, Violet, please.
好了 没事了
It's all right.It's all right.
我们错过了什么
What have we missed.
我认识你
I know you.
你女朋友的事我很抱歉
I'm sorry about your girl.
但是她妨碍到我了
But she was in the way.
我知道你会理解我的 一定会的
You understand.I know you do.
他们是怪物
They're monsters.
我只看到一个怪物
I only see one monster here.
你还好吗
You're alright.
会好起来的 你呢
I will be.You.
我过段时间再告诉你情况吧
I'll get back to you on that.
Sal 他说他很抱歉
Sal, he said he was sorry.
这是他的遗言
Those were his last words.
David 对不起 我是迫不得已
David, I'm sorry.I didn't have a choice.
但是Sal从来没对我做过什么
But Sal never did anything to me.
为什么他会这么说
Why would he say that.
Sal 你在这里干什么
Sal, what are you doing.
他不会来了 对不对
He isn't coming, is he.
David很快就会到
David will be here in a few minutes.
但你不能待在这
You won't be.
你为什么要这么做
Why are you doing this.
因为他是我弟弟 Violet
Cause he is my little brother, Violet.
保护他是我的职责
It's my job to protect him.
我必须保证我们的血统纯洁
It's my job to keep our blood pure.
你相信血脉那些鬼话
You believe that bloodline crap.
我们都相信
We all do.
血统
Bloodlines.
这是唯一的
Everyone knows our places is the one thing.
我们所有人都认同的事情
We all agree on.
一旦他们发现你和一个变形怪一起逃跑了
If you people find out that you run out with a shifter.
他们会想方设法报仇的
They will be looking for pay back.
他们会对我的家族穷追不舍
They will come after my family.
这样只会两败俱伤
It's nothing but bad times and dead bodies, on both sides.
David想要离开 那是他的选择
David wants to go straight, that's his call.
但那只是他一个人
But he does it alone.
Violet 你还有别的选择
So you have a choice, Violet.
你可以活着离开这里
You can either walk out of here alive.
否则我会带你离开
Or I will take you out.
然后把你扔进湖里
And dumped what's left of you in the lake.
Sal
Sal.
我爱他
I love him.
那又能怎样呢
I wish that matters.
即使我离开了我的家族
Even after I left my family.
我也知道事情不妙了
I knew things got bad.
但是Sal会一直支持我的
And Sal would always have my back.
所以
So.
他到底是什么意思
What did he mean.
我不知道
I don't know.
我应该离开了
I should go.
当然
Sure, right.
逃跑是你最擅长的
That's what you do best.
David
David.
爸爸
Pop.
你说什么
What.
你的妹妹
Your sister.
她要挑起战争
She wants war.
你必须阻止她
You have to stop her.
这些不过是个喝醉了的家伙弄的
All these was some messed up guy.
Duvals都没有问题
The Duvals are clean.
好吧 我们完事了吗
Fine, we done.
我打算重回家族里
I'm coming back to the family.
我以为你已经离开家族了
I thought you were out.
但是如今我决定回来
And now I am back in.
为你这句话我已经等了太久
I've waited long time to hear you say that.
欢迎回家 David
Welcome home, David.
你一个人住这里吗
You live here alone.
我姐姐住在镇子另一边
My sister is on the other side of the town.
母亲离婚了
My mom is out of the picture.
我父亲 嗯 他殉职了
My dad, well, he died, line of duty.
很久以前的事了
Long time ago.
我很抱歉
Sorry to hear that.
喂
Yeah.
好的
Okay.
好 我们这就上路
Yeah, we are on our way, yeah.
稍等一会
Just give me a second.
- 怎么了 - 我们得离开这了
- Yeah - We got a gig.
离开 为什么
You wanna leave.
Dean 这城里可是挤满了怪物
Dean, this city is crawling with monsters.
Cass有Metatron的消息了
Cass has a line on Metatron.
我们一直在等的不就是这个吗
This is what we've been waiting for.
我们的机会来了 Sam
It's our shot, Sam.
你们要走了吗
You're going.
听着 我们会找其他的猎人来
Look, we will call some other hunters, some pros.
然后解决掉这些怪物黑帮 所有的
And download them on the monster mob situation, all of it.
伙计们 我自己就可以
Guys, I could.
不行 我是认真的 你不能自己去
Don't, seriously, don't.
一旦陷得太深 你就永远不可能脱身了
You getting in this too deep, there is no way getting out.
但是我不可能就这样抽身
But I couldn't walk away.
如今 这是属于我的战斗
This is my fight, now.
见鬼的 战争开始了
Hell, it's a damn war.
我得找个地方开始
And I gotta start somewhere.
残酷恶行
Vicious Mauling.
死亡惨剧震惊全城
Tragic Death Shocks the City.
来电 号码未知
Incoming…unknown caller.
喂
Hello.
你这是在做什么
What are you doing.
你是谁
Who is this.
如果你开始猎魔
If you start hunting.
那些怪物会把你生吞活剥了的
The monsters will kill you.
爸爸
Dad.